

### CONTACT ME AT

Phone : 087783877452

Email : dian.agustina206@gmail.com

Linked in : dian agustina

Github : https://dianagustina19.github.io/

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

- Html5
- PHP
- MySQL
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Css
- Bootstrap
- SQL Server
- Oracle
- Laravel Framework

### LANGUAGE

- <u>B</u>ahasa
- English

# **DIAN AGUSTINA**

# WEB DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Graduated with a bachelor's degree in information system from Gunadarma University. I am a person who has passion and good discipline that is always applied.

Good at analyst, planning and communication, I am very passionate in doing website development, and i have experience creating website.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **PHP Programmer**

PT Pro Sigmaka Mandiri | August 2021 - Present

- Add Features to Existing Websites
- Add a Security Assessment on the Website

# Software Engineer Front End

PT Rupi Digital Indonesia | August 2020 - May 2021

- Build Web Monitoring Using Laravel Framework
- Build Web Reporting Using Laravel Framework
- Build Web Integrated API
- Add Features to Existing Websites
- Using Scrum Method

# Web Developer

PT Tripasysfo Development | October 2019 - May 2020

 Build The Whole Backend For Reporting Website Using Laravel Framework

#### PERSONAL PROJECT

1. Freelance

- Client : PT. Karya Utama Gama (KUGAMA) Make some modules using laravel framework.

- Client: PT. Musik Hanamidori

Develop Company Profile Using PHP and Mysql

#### EDUCATION

# **Gunadarma University**

Information System | 2015 - 2019

Last GPA: 3.43